http://www.fuel.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us. At Fuel International we have a few fundamental principles:
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
Fuel International operates several websites including Fuel.org and FuelGhana.org. It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Fuel International collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Fuel International’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Fuel International’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Fuel International may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Fuel International also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Fuel International operated websites. Fuel International only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Fuel International’s websites choose to interact with Fuel International in ways that require Fuel International to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Fuel International gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up as a user on Fuel.org to leave comments are asked to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Fuel International – by making donations online, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Fuel International collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Fuel International. Fuel International does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Fuel International may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Fuel International may monitor the most popular pages and comments on its sites. Fuel International may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Fuel International does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Fuel International discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Fuel International’s behalf or to provide services available at Fuel International’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Fuel International’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Fuel International will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Fuel International discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Fuel International believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Fuel International, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Fuel International website and have supplied your email address, Fuel International may occasionally send you an email to tell you about website updates, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Fuel International and our projects. We primarily use our various websites to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Fuel International takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Fuel International uses cookies to help Fuel International identify and track visitors, their usage of Fuel International websites, and their website access preferences. Fuel International visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Fuel International’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Fuel International’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Fuel International, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Fuel International goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Fuel International may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Fuel International and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Comments
Comments and other content submitted to Fuel International sites are saved and sometimes published publicly. Only leave comments on Fuel International sites that you are comfortable with being publicly displayed.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Fuel International may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Fuel International’s sole discretion. Fuel International encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Privacy Policy
